Jarosław Wygoda

Python Developer Born 1996 in Kraków



About me

Hi, my name is Jarosław Wygoda. I'm more than a programmer, I'm a problem solver. My day-to-day work involves understanding business needs and expressing it in software. I'm a back end engineer with strong devops skills and experience in developing user interfaces.

My main domain of expertise are Django web applications.

Skills



Contact





48517663382



jwygoda



Experience

Homeppl

since May 2020

As a consultant I've helped Homeppl team migrate django application to microservices architecture.

PatientSource

October 2019 - April 2020

As a consultant I've helped PatientSource team introduce devops-centered development process and support them with day-to-day development process.

Netguru

October 2018 - September 2019

Developing platform managing and optimising online advertising campaigns. Collaborating with London based advertising agency. Supporting R&D initiatives, estimating projects, presales activities, participating in scoping sessions and expert calls, code reviews. Technologies: Python, Django, Postgres, Docker, Terraform, CloudFormation, Zappa (serverless), AWS services, BigQuery, Git

WhiteAster

January 2018 - October 2018

Integrating machine learning solutions. Collaborating with New York based fintech company providing daily cashflow to Amazon suppliers. Technologies: Python, Django, Flask, TensorFlow, Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, JavaScript, Vue.js, AWS services, Git

Freelancing

October 2016 - January 2018

Developing e-commerce platforms, content management systems, web scraping scripts and payment gateways. Some projects I worked on: Project management system and lead generation scripts for advertisement company Q-Graf. Payment system for Tylicz ski resort. Technologies: Python, Django, Wagtail, django-payments, Saleor, Docker, Javascript, Git



Education

Music School - Cello 2008 - 2016 I was going to be a musician before I fell in love with programming.



Contributions

Django

Added support for PEP 487 to Django models.

https://github.com/django/django

google-ads-python

Added support for loading config from environment variables. https://github.com/googleads/googleads-python